Guide to the Time Inc. Time Research Center Files 1919-2015 MS 3009-RG 13
New-York Historical Society
- Series III. Subject Files, 1926-2000; 774 Linear feet (774 boxes)
  - United States
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Campaigns: Espionage and sabotage, 1972-1990 (Offsite-box 2067, Folder 1-30)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Campaigns: Espionage and sabotage, 1973-1992 (Offsite-box 2068, Folder 1-35)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Campaigns: Espionage and sabotage, 1973-1987 (Offsite-box 2069, Folder 1-34)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Campaigns: Espionage and sabotage, 1973-1982 (Offsite-box 2070, Folder 1-19)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Campaigns: Espionage and sabotage, 1972-1992 (Offsite-box 2071, Folder 1-30)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Campaigns: Espionage and sabotage, 1958-1993 (Offsite-box 2072, Folder 1-28)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Campaigns: Negative, 1980-1986 (Offsite-box 2104, Folder 1)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Campaigns: Transportation, 1968-1992 (Offsite-box 2104, Folder 2)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Campaigns: Truth squads, 1964-1988 (Offsite-box 2104, Folder 3)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Campaigns: Whistle stops, 1976-1992 (Offsite-box 2104, Folder 4)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Candidates: General-Assassinations, 1930-1992 (Offsite-box 2104, Folder 5-34)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Candidates: Assassinations-Dark Horse, 1968-1993 (Offsite-box 2105, Folder 1-16)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Candidates: Dead-Extramarial Relations, 1935-1993 (Offsite-box 2106, Folder 1-24)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Candidates: Extramarital Relations-Finance, 1952-1992 (Offsite-box 2107, Folder 1-20)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Candidates: Finance-Image, 1952-1993 (Offsite-box 2108, Folder 1-22)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Candidates: Image-Incumbents, 1968-1993 (Offsite-box 2109, Folder 1-14)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Candidates: Incumbents-Independent, 1962-1989 (Offsite-box 2110, Folder 1-18)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Candidates: Liquor Drinking-Religion, 1958-1993 (Offsite-box 2111, Folder 1-22)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Candidates: Religion-Withdrawal, 1937-1992 (Offsite-box 2112, Folder 1-22)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Candidates: Withdrawal-Women, 1968-1993 (Offsite-box 2113, Folder 1-22)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Candidates: Women, 1972-1977 (Offsite-box 2114, Folder 1-2)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Certificates, 1968-1993 (Offsite-box 2114, Folder 3)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Congressional, 1953-1993 (Offsite-box 2114, Folder 4-13)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Conventions, 1938-1992 (Offsite-box 2114, Folder 14-17)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Conventions: Mock conventions, 1971-1972 (Offsite-box 2114, Folder 18)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Effects, 1976-1992 (Offsite-box 2114, Folder 19)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Election district, 1956-1992 (Offsite-box 2114, Folder 20-21)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Finance, 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 2114, Folder 22-23)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Finance, 1974-1986 (Offsite-box 2115, Folder 1-16)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Finance, 1937-1973 (Offsite-box 2116, Folder 1-21)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Finance, 1974-1993 (Offsite-box 2117, Folder 1-24)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Finance, 1975-1993 (Offsite-box 2118, Folder 1-3)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Forecasting, 1985-1992 (Offsite-box 2118, Folder 4)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Foreign reactions, 1956-1992 (Offsite-box 2118, Folder 5-6)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Frauds, 1936-1992 (Offsite-box 2118, Folder 7-8)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Gubernatorial, 1942-1992 (Offsite-box 2118, Folder 9)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: History, 1938-1992 (Offsite-box 2118, Folder 10-15)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Issues, 1968-1993 (Offsite-box 2118, Folder 16-23)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Judicial, 1986-1992 (Offsite-box 2118, Folder 24)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Key areas, 1950-1992 (Offsite-box 2118, Folder 25-27)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Legislation, 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 2118, Folder 28)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Legislation, 1954-1992 (Offsite-box 2119, Folder 1-28)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Legislation, 1965-1992 (Offsite-box 2120, Folder 1-20)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Legislation, 1965 (Offsite-box 2121, Folder 1)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Merchandising, 1984-1988 (Offsite-box 2121, Folder 2)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Mock elections, 1967-1992 (Offsite-box 2121, Folder 3)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: News coverage, 1956-1993 (Offsite-box 2121, Folder 4-15)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Personnel, 1988-1993 (Offsite-box 2121, Folder 16-21)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Personnel, 1961-1988 (Offsite-box 2122, Folder 1-17)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Platforms, 1956-1992 (Offsite-box 2122, Folder 18)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Polls, 1969-1992 (Offsite-box 2122, Folder 19-22)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Polls, 1944-1968 (Offsite-box 2123, Folder 1-4)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Primaries, 1938-1993 (Offsite-box 2123, Folder 5-29)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Recounts, 1963-1981 (Offsite-box 2123, Folder 30)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Registration, 1957-1977 (Offsite-box 2123, Folder 31-35)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Registration, 1956 (Offsite-box 2145, Folder 1)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Runoffs, 1968-1993 (Offsite-box 2145, Folder 2)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: State and local caucuses and conventions, 1976-1992 (Offsite-box 2145, Folder 3)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Task forces, 1976-1981 (Offsite-box 2145, Folder 4)
    - United States: Politics: Elections: Trends, 1952-1992 (Offsite-box 2145, Folder 5-16)
    - United States: Population: General, 1987-1993 (Offsite-box 2145, Folder 17-25)
    - United States: Population: General, 1930-1986 (Offsite-box 2146, Folder 1-23)
    - United States: Population: A, 1978-1993 (Offsite-box 2146, Folder 24)
    - United States: Population: Acadians, 1939-1990 (Offsite-box 2146, Folder 25-26)
    - United States: Population: Africans, 1961-1993 (Offsite-box 2146, Folder 27)
    - United States: Population: Albanians, 1936-1992 (Offsite-box 2146, Folder 28)
    - United States: Population: Amerasians, 1982-1992 (Offsite-box 2147, Folder 1)
    - United States: Population: Arab-Americans, 1988-1993 (Offsite-box 2147, Folder 2)
    - United States: Population: Arabs, 1946-1993 (Offsite-box 2147, Folder 3-7)
    - United States: Population: Armenians, 1971-1991 (Offsite-box 2147, Folder 8)
    - United States: Population: Asian-Americans, 1991-1993 (Offsite-box 2147, Folder 9)
    - United States: Population: Asians, 1960-1993 (Offsite-box 2147, Folder 10-21)
    - United States: Population: Australians, 1962-1986 (Offsite-box 2147, Folder 22)
    - United States: Population: Austrians, 1943-1979 (Offsite-box 2147, Folder 23)
    - United States: Population: B, 1959-1991 (Offsite-box 2147, Folder 24)
    - United States: Population: Basques, 1959-1986 (Offsite-box 2148, Folder 1)
    - United States: Population: Birth rate, 1934-1992 (Offsite-box 2148, Folder 2-19)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: General, 1988-1993 (Offsite-box 2148, Folder 20-24)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: General, 1977-1987 (Offsite-box 2149, Folder 1-9)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Agriculture, 1977-1992 (Offsite-box 2149, Folder 10)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Associations, 1961-1993 (Offsite-box 2149, Folder 11-37)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Associations, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 2150, Folder 1-20)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Associations, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 2151, Folder 1-32)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Associations, 1977-1985 (Offsite-box 2152, Folder 1-2)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Awards, 1979-1992 (Offsite-box 2152, Folder 4)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Black consciousness, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 2152, Folder 5)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Black market, 1981-1993 (Offsite-box 2152, Folder 6-8)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Black nationalism, 1979-1993 (Offsite-box 2152, Folder 9)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Black power, 1980-1993 (Offsite-box 2152, Folder 10)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Business, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 2152, Frame 11-20)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Conferences, 1980-1991 (Offsite-box 2152, Folder 21)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Demonstrations, 1961-1993 (Offsite-box 2152, Folder 22-35)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Demonstrations, 1977-1992 (Offsite-box 2153, Folder 1-10)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Demonstrations, 1977-1992 (Offsite-box 1784, Folder 3)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 2153, Folder 11-28)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 2154, Folder 1-30)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 2155, Folder 1-45)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 2156, Folder 1-36)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination, 1976-1993 (Offsite-box 2157, Folder 1-34)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Education, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 2158, Folder 1-32)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Foreign relations, 1979-1993 (Offsite-box 2158, Folder 33)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Government relations, 1978-1993 (Offsite-box 2158, Folder 34)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Gullah, 1982-1992 (Offsite-box 2159, Folder 1)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: History, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 2159, Folder 2-11)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Inter-black relations, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 2159, Folder 12)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Leadership, 1979-1993 (Offsite-box 2159, Folder 13-27)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Leadership, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 2160, Folder 1-2)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Migration, 1977-1992 (Offsite-box 2160, Folder 3)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Militancy, 1977-1985 (Offsite-box 2160, Folder 4)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: News coverage, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 2160, Folder 5)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Passing, 1977-1989 (Offsite-box 2160, Folder 6)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Politics, 1986-1993 (Offsite-box 2160, Folder 7-15)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Politics, 1977-1990 (Offsite-box 2161, Folder 1-14)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Polls, 1977-1992 (Offsite-box 2162, Folder 1)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Population statistics, 1979-1993 (Offsite-box 2162, Folder 2)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Preferential treatment, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 2162, Folder 3)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Professions, 1981-1991 (Offsite-box 2162, Folder 4)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Publications, 1979-1991 (Offsite-box 2162, Folder 5)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Records (documents), 1984-1986 (Offsite-box 2162, Folder 6)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Records (superlatives), 1978-1989 (Offsite-box 2162, Folder 7)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Regions, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 2162, Folder 8-11)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Reparations, 1987-1992 (Offsite-box 2162, Folder 12)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Research, 1990-1992 (Offsite-box 2162, Folder 13)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Riots, 1980-1993 (Offsite-box 2162, Folder 14-24)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Riots, 1973-1993 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 1-15)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Shows, 1963-1991 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 16)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Alabama, 1978-1992 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 17-23)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Arizona, 1984-1987 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 24)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Arkansas, 1981-1992 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 25-26)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: California, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 27-29)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Colorado, 1981-1991 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 30)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Connecticut, 1980-1993 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 31)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Delaware, 1980-1986 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 32)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: District of Columbia, 1978-1993 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 33)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Florida, 1980-1993 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 34-36)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Georgia, 1978-1993 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 37-38)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Georgia, 1977-1992 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 1-2)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Idaho, 1991 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 3)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Illinois, 1973-1992 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 4-8)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Indiana, 1984-1992 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 9)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Iowa, 1984-1991 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 10)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Kansas, 1977-1991 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 11)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Kentucky, 1988-1991 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 12)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Louisiana, 1982-1993 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 13-14)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Maine, 1987-1991 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 15)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Maryland, 1981-1993 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 16-18)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Massachusetts, 1979-1992 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 19-20)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Michigan, 1978-1993 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 21-23)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Minnesota, 1992 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 24)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Mississippi, 1979-1993 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 25-32)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Missouri, 1977-1991 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 33-35)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Montana, 1990-1992 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 36)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Nebraska, 1980-1990 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 37)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Nevada, 1992 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 38)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: New Hampshire, 1991 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 39)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: New Jersey, 1979-1993 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 40-41)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: New York, 1989-1993 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 42-46)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: New York, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 1-9)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: North Carolina, 1980-1993 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 10-12)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Ohio, 1978-1993 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 13-15)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Oklahoma, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 16)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Oregon, 1985 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 17)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Pennsylvania, 1986-1993 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 18-19)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Rhode Island, 1988 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 20)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: South Carolina, 1981-1992 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 21)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Tennessee, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 22-24)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Texas, 1978-1992 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 25-28)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Utah, 1978-1992 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 29)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Vermont, 1987 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 30)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Virginia, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 31-33)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Washington, 1989 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 34)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: West Virginia, 1988 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 35)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Wisconsin, 1979-1992 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 36-37)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Suburban "blacks" [African Americans], 1979-1989 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 38)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Urban "blacks" [African Americans], 1981-1993 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 39-40)
    - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Urban "blacks" [African Americans], 1977-1980 (Offsite-box 2228, Folder 1-2)
    - United States: Population: British, 1976-1993 (Offsite-box 2228, Folder 3)
    - United States: Population: C, 1979-1991 (Offsite-box 2228, Folder 4)
    - United States: Population: Cambodians, 1985-1991 (Offsite-box 2228, Folder 5)
    - United States: Population: Canadians, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 2228, Folder 6)
    - United States: Population: Center of, 1951-1971 (Offsite-box 2228, Folder 7)
    - United States: Population: Chinese, 1930-1992 (Offsite-box 2228, Folder 8-27)
    - United States: Population: Colombians, 1985-1993 (Offsite-box 2228, Folder 28)
    - United States: Population: Croatians, 1977-1992 (Offsite-box 2228, Folder 29)
    - United States: Population: Cubans, 1987-1993 (Offsite-box 2228, Folder 30-33)
    - United States: Population: Cubans, 1954-1986 (Offsite-box 2229, Folder 1-13)
    - United States: Population: Czechoslovakians, 1938-1992 (Offsite-box 2229, Folder 14)
    - United States: Population: D, 1953-1989 (Offsite-box 2229, Folder 15)
    - United States: Population: Dominicans, 1952-1993 (Offsite-box 2229, Folder 16-18)
    - United States: Population: E, 1960-1993 (Offsite-box 2229, Folder 19)
    - United States: Population: Enemy aliens, 1945-1975 (Offsite-box 2229, Folder 20)
    - United States: Population: Eskimos, 1959-1993 (Offsite-box 2229, Folder 21)
    - United States: Population: F, 1971-1988 (Offsite-box 2229, Folder 22)
    - United States: Population: Filipinos, 1984-1993 (Offsite-box 2229, Folder 23)
    - United States: Population: Finns, 1939-1990 (Offsite-box 2229, Folder 24)
    - United States: Population: Foreigners, 1972-1993 (Offsite-box 2229, Folder 25-32)
    - United States: Population: Foreigners, 1938-1986 (Offsite-box 2230, Folder 1-7)
    - United States: Population: French, 1939-1993 (Offsite-box 2230, Folder 8)
    - United States: Population: G, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 2230, Folder 9)
    - United States: Population: Germans, 1924-1993 (Offsite-box 2230, Folder 10-12)
    - United States: Population: Greeks, 1932-1992 (Offsite-box 2230, Folder 13-17)
    - United States: Population: H, 1965-1993 (Offsite-box 2230, Folder 18)
    - United States: Population: Haitians, 1957-1993 (Offsite-box 2230, Folder 19-24)
    - United States: Population: Hungarians, 1939-1990 (Offsite-box 2230, Folder 25-28)
    - United States: Population: I, 1987-1992 (Offsite-box 2230, Folder 29)
    - United States: Population: "Indians" [Native Americans]: General, 1986-1993 (Offsite-box 2230, Folder 30-32)
    - United States: Population: "Indians" [Native Americans]: General, 1937-1985 (Offsite-box 2231, Folder 1-16)
    - United States: Population: "Indians" [Native Americans]: Associations, 1950-1992 (Offsite-box 2231, Folder 17-43)
    - United States: Population: "Indians" [Native Americans]: Awards, 1952-1991 (Offsite-box 2231, Folder 44)
    - United States: Population: "Indians" [Native Americans]: Business, 1973-1993 (Offsite-box 2231, Folder 45)
    - United States: Population: "Indians" [Native Americans]: Clothing, 1934-1990 (Offsite-box 2232, Folder 1)
    - United States: Population: "Indians" [Native Americans]: Conferences, 1972-1990 (Offsite-box 2232, Folder 2)
    - United States: Population: "Indians" [Native Americans]: Consciousness, 1974-1991 (Offsite-box 2232, Folder 3)
    - United States: Population: "Indians" [Native Americans]: Courts, 1971-1991 (Offsite-box 2232, Folder 4)
    - United States: Population: "Indians" [Native Americans]: Culture, 1925-1993 (Offsite-box 2232, Folder 5-13)
    - United States: Population: "Indians" [Native Americans]: Demonstrations, 1975-1992 (Offsite-box 2232, Folder 14)
    - United States: Population: "Indians" [Native Americans]: Discrimination, 1947-1993 (Offsite-box 2232, Folder 15-19)
    - United States: Population: "Indians" [Native Americans]: Education, 1937-1993 (Offsite-box 2232, Folder 20-27)
    - United States: Population: "Indians" [Native Americans]: Finance, 1976-1993 (Offsite-box 2232, Folder 28)
    - United States: Population: "Indians" [Native Americans]: Gambling, 1990-1993 (Offsite-box 2232, Folder 29-30)
    - United States: Population: "Indians" [Native Americans]: Gambling, 1984-1989 (Offsite-box 2233, Folder 1)
    - United States: Population: "Indians" [Native Americans]: Government relations, 1975-1993 (Offsite-box 2233, Folder 2-6)